<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SkillMaster</string>
    <string name="pp">Please note Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. By continuing to use the Site, you are accepting our privacy policy and terms of use stated herein.

\n\nPrivacy Policy &amp; Legal Terms of Use
\nBy accessing all or any part of this website (the "Site”), you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use (this "Agreement”).  If you do not agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use you should not access or view this Site.

\n\nDisclaimer
\nBy use of any information and hyperlinks (collectively called "Materials"), or purchase of any products or services (collectively called "Products”) communicated through this Internet Web site, list-server, e-mail server, domain name server (collectively called "Service”), you hereby acknowledge, and agree to the following:

\n\nWe and our dealers, associates, agents and licensors expressly do not make any warranties, including, without limitation, warranties of fitness for a particular purpose, as well as warranties of accuracy, completeness, currentness, non-infringement, merchantability with respect to the Service, the Materials, or the Products provided or offered here.

\n\nNeither we nor any of our dealers, associates, agents and licensors shall be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, or consequential loss, damage or injury of any kind whatsoever in connection with the Service, even if advised on the possibility of such damages. By using the Service you assume full responsibilty.

\n\nBy using the Service you assume full responsibility for the use of all Materials and Products. You assume full responsibility for adherence to any and all applicable laws and regulations, including local, governing professional licensing, advertising, business practices, and all other aspects of doing business in Singapore or any other jurisdiction. Any Materials, Products, and offerings are void where prohibited by law.

\n\nTrademarks
\nAll trademarks or registered trademarks are property of their respective owners. Usage of other trademarks is only for illustrative, educational, or entertainment purposes, without intent to infringe. Any such trademark usage does not constitute endorsement by PAWER SKILLS or any of its dealers, associates, affiliates, licensors. Any perceived slight of existing entities is purely coincidental and not intentional.

\n\nCopyright
\nUnless where indicated otherwise, copyright for all materials © 2015 PAWER SKILLS CONSULTANCY....., ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. Text, images, graphics and HTML code are protected by Singapore and international copyright laws.  By submitting unsolicited Material submitted through the Service, you agree that such material shall become the property of PAWER SKILLS unless indicated or agreed upon otherwise.

\n\nNo translation or reproduction, either electronically or mechanically, permitted without express written permission from PAWER SKILLS. Any violation of our copyrights, patents or trademarks will be quickly prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.

\n\nPrivacy Statement
\nFor each visit to our Web site, our Web server automatically recognizes only the visitor's IP address, but not the email address, unless the visitor volunteers their e-mail address to us by filling out a web form.

\n\nWe electronically collect the e-mail addresses of those who complete online web forms, of those who communicate with us via e-mail, of those who make purchases, etc.

\n\nThe information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web site, used to notify users about updates to our Web site and used by us to contact user for marketing purposes target to users' specific needs.

\n\nIf you do not want to receive e-mails from us in the future, please let us know by sending an e-mail to us at feedback@pawer.com.sg and tell us that you do not want to receive e-mails from our company. We will then, to the best of our abilities, remove your e-mail address from our databases and Web site.

\n\nWe have implemented reasonable technology and security policies, procedures and other measures that are intended to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, and accidental loss. We also endeavor to protect your information by requiring that all our personnel, employees and others who have access to or are associated with the processing of your data respect your confidentiality. In addition, we have reasonable security measures in place in our physical facilities intended to protect against the loss or misuse of information at our site that we have collected from you.  However, you must carefully consider what information you share with us, as we cannot guarantee that we will be able to block all attempted attacks to the security of our Site.

\n\nIf you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by sending an e-mail to us at the above address or writing to us at the above address.

\n\nChanges in Legal Terms of Use
\nThese terms of use are subject to change at any time, without notice. All changes to these Terms of Use are published here; for the latest version check this page.

\n\nEffective as of Dec 2014

</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
